♪ Sometimes I'm right and I can be wrong ♪
♪ My own beliefs are in my song ♪
♪ The butcher, the banker,
the drummer and then ♪
♪ Makes no difference what group I'm in ♪
♪ I am everyday people, yeah yeah ♪
♪ There is a blue one who
can't accept the green one ♪
♪ For living with a fat one
trying to be a skinny one ♪
♪ And different strokes
for different folks ♪
♪ And so on and so on and
scooby dooby doo-bee ♪
♪ Ooh sha sha, we got to live together ♪
♪ I am no better and neither are you ♪
♪ We are the same whatever we do ♪
♪ You love me, you hate
me, you know me and then ♪
♪ You can't figure out the bag I'm in ♪
♪ I am everyday people, yeah yeah ♪
♪ There is a long hair that
doesn't like the short hair ♪
♪ For bein' such a rich one that
will not help the poor one ♪
♪ And different strokes
for different folks ♪
♪ And so on and so on and
scooby dooby doo-bee ♪
♪ Ooh sha sha, we got to live together ♪
♪ There is a yellow one that
won't accept the black one ♪
♪ That won't accept the red one ♪
♪ That won't accept the white one ♪
♪ And different strokes
for different folks ♪
♪ And so on and so on and
scooby dooby doo-bee ♪
♪ Ooh, sha sha ♪
♪ I am everyday people ♪